Kambale Mechack

Web Developer



Profile

Web enthusiast and technology, I'm a web developer since more than 4 years now. I've been working as a Frontend developer for 3 years at HPS Dev and Design, I designed several projects. Since 2019, I decided to become a full stack developer and I started by learning NodeJs and Express.

Personal Information

d , Kampala, Uganda

+256752949545

in Mechack Makasi

Mechack Kobius Makasi

@MakasiMechack

(i) mechackmakasi

Professional experience

Front-end developer, HPS Design

03 2018 - 05 2022

Kampala

As a web developer I worked on several projects, sometimes under clients pressure or team mates despite all those pressures I'm happy because it made me stronger. I developed projects such as an E-commerce web application, Schools websites, Portfolios and many other projects.

Front-end developer, Vodacom

07 2017 - 01 2018

Ben

A professional training, after getting my bachelor. I learned how to work as a professional web developer.

Professional skills

HTML

Expert

CSS

Avancé

JavaScript

Intermédiaire

React Js

Avancé

Redux

Avancé

Adobe XD

Intermédiaire

Education

IT management, Adventist University of Lukanga 10 2018 - 12 2020

Butembo, Democratique Republic of Congo

Economics and IT management, Adventist 10 2015 - 07 2018

Butembo, Democratique Republic of Congo

References

Enoch Wanzaluendo - PAM

University of Lukanga

enowanzaluendo@gmail.com - +243811493857

Ange, Neema Muhimiri - PAF AFRICA

amuhimirineema@gmail.com - +243971062572

Professional skills

Node Js

Intermédiaire

Axios

Avancé

Languages

French

Native

English

Fluent

Swahili

Fluent